Guide to the Abe Burrows papers, 1904-1993
The New York Public Library. Billy Rose Theatre Division.
- Series I: Personal Correspondence and Other Papers, 1904-1985; 588239; 4 boxes
  - Sub-series 3 - Personal Files, 1904-1981 and n.d; 588287; 21 folders
    - Miscellaneous awards and certificates,., 1947-1979; 588303; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Personal ephemera / Abe Burrows, 1960-1979 and n.d; 588304; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Personal ephemera consists of social security cards, a list of professional credits, membership cards, certificates and correspondence, invitation and program for his induction into the Theater Hall of Fame in 1979.
    - Correspondence / Abe Burrows,., 1951-1979; 588305; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Printed invitations sent to Abe Burrows and his wife.
    - Personal ephemera / Abe Burrows, 1947-1980 and n.d; 588306; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Printed programs reflecting Abe Burrows' career.
    - Personal ephemera / Abe Burrows, 1904-1950 and n.d; 588307; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Miscellaneous ephemera includes tickets for Burrows shows 1947-1949, metal plates for card printing, a list of theatrical celebrities prepared for Burrows, handwritten sheet music (2 p.), a postcard of Provincetown, a photograph of Abe Burrows with his friend Sam Hearn, a 1904 commencement program for CCNY, and a few other items.
    - Correspondence / Abe Burrows,., 1961-1980; 588308; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Correspondence with various institutions each hoping to become the repository for Abe Burrows Papers.
  - Sub-series 4 - Condolences, 1985 and n.d; 588309; 5 folders
    This sub-series contains funeral parlor registers and condolence letters and cards received by Carin Burrows after the death of Abe Burrows. It also includes her record of condolences received and one undated condolence card sent after her death.
    - Funeral parlor registers,., 1985; 588310; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Two funeral parlor registers for Abe Burrows.
    - Condolence correspondence, A-K,., 1985; 588311; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Letters to Carin Burrows on the death of her husband, Abe Burrows.
    - Condolence correspondence, L-Z,., 1985; 588312; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Condolence correspondence,., 1985; 588313; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 17)
      Condolence letters and gift cards [from unidentified correspondents] to Carin Burrows on the death of her husband, Abe Burrows.
    - Condolence Records,., 1985; 588314; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Carin Burrows' record of condolences received on the death of her husband, Abe Burrows, and one card [n.d., addressee unknown] sent by a neighbor in her apartment building after Carin's death.
- Series II: General Correspondence, 1939-1982; 588315; 15 boxes
  Correspondence and telegrams document the life and career of Abe Burrows. While most family letters are in Series I, Burrows' personal and professional life were deeply intertwined; his colleagues were his friends. Thus there is not a clear divide between personal and professional letters, and many insights on Burrows the man can be found here.
  Letters are arranged alphabetically by correspondent and telegrams are arranged chronologically by production.
  - Sub-series 1 - Letters, 1939-1982; 588316; 12 boxes
    This sub-series of both personal and professional correspondence is arranged alphabetically with incoming letters and carbons of Burrows' replies kept together. Folders are for individual correspondent for prominent and/or prolific writers, followed by miscellaneous groupings for each letter of the alphabet. The letters range from substantive correspondence with colleagues such as Harry Kurnitz, Frank Loesser and Cole Porter, to extensive correspondence on arrangements and complaints with car rental agencies and department stores. Burrows was an inveterate letter writer and his many correspondents included Fred Allen, Steve Allen, Woody Allen, Mac Benoff, Richard Bissell, Bernard Braden, Art Buchwald, Eddie Cantor, Noel Coward, Fleur Cowles, Bing Crosby, Robert Emmet Dolan, Cy Feuer, Pierre Galante, Ed Gardner, Oscar Hammerstein, Julie Harris, Moss Hart, Lester Hyman, Belinda Jelliffe, Nunnally Johnson, E. J. Kahn, Lawrence Kasha, Madeleine Kasket, George S. Kaufman, Elia and Molly Kazan, Jean Kerr, Sidney Kingsley, Sam Levene, Art Lewis, Howard Lindsay and Russel Crouse, Joshua Logan, Philip Malicoat, Groucho Marx, Ken McCormick, Shepherd Mead, Jo Mielziner, Edwin O'Connor, Richard Rodgers, Billy Rose, Sam Rosenberg, Harry Ruby, Phil Silvers, John Steinbeck, Jule Styne, Rudy Vallee, Herman Wouk, Maurice Zolotow and Albert Zuckerman among others. This sub-series also includes correspondence with professional organizations such as the Dramatists Guild.
    In 1951 Burrows was subpoenaed by the House Committee on Un-American Activities and attempted to cooperate by testifying. He was not charged or blacklisted though in 1954 he still experienced some problems with potential sponsors because of the fact that he had been subpoenaed. His testimony, later statements, correspondence with his lawyers and letters he received from the public are filed here under "HUAC".
    - Correspondence / George Abbott,., 1953-1964; 588317; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Letters of thanks to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Actors' Fund of America,., 1972-1977; 588318; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Letters and receipts to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Richard Adler,., 1961; 588319; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Edward Albee, 588320; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 4)
      One letter of thanks for an opening night telegram to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Alan Alda,., 1967 Jan; 588321; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Correspondence (2 letters) between Alda and Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Fred Allen,., 1944-1961; 588322; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence / Steve Allen,., 1959-1969; 588323; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence / Woody Allen,., 1955-1969; 588324; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence / American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers,., 1952-1987; 588325; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Correspondence and financial and legal records with or about Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / John Murray Anderson,., 1952; 588326; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence / Robert Woodruff Anderson,., 1971-1972; 588327; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence / Jean Pierre Aumont,., 1953; 588328; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence / Gene Autry,., 1948 Dec 30; 588329; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 13)
      One letter with envelope to Abe Burrows.
    - General correspondence, "Ab-Ai",., 1946-1978; 588330; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Correspondence, both personal and professional, of Abe Burrows.
    - General correspondence, "Al",., 1951-1980; 588331; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - General correspondence, "Am-Ax",., 1949-1981; 588332; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Correspondence, both personal and professional, of Abe Burrows. Includes a letter, 1964 Jan 5, from Elizabeth Ashley thanking him for his opening night wire.
    - Correspondence / Binnie Barnes,., 1949 July; 588333; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Two letters to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Philip Barry,., 1960; 588334; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence / Sir Cecil Walter Hardy Beaton,., 1952; 588335; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence / S. N. (Samuel Nathaniel) Behrman,., 1968-1969; 588336; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence / Mac Benoff,., 1941-1955; 588337; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence / Mac Benoff,., 1956-1972; 588338; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence / Milton Berle,., 1949 May 16; 588339; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 23)
      One letter of thanks to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Irving Berlin,., 1953-1962; 588340; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Two letters to Abe Burrows, one with a letter to Cole Porter enclosed.
    - Correspondence / Leonard Bernstein,., 1956-1977; 588341; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Correspondence between Leonard and Felicia Bernstein and Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Theodore Bikel,., 1959-1971; 588342; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 26)
      Three letters and a card to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Richard Pike Bissell,., 1957-1980; 588343; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Correspondence between Richard and Marion Bissell and Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Shirley Booth,., 1952-1962; 588344; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence / Bernard Braden,., 1953-1969; 588345; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence / Frederick Brisson,., 1954-1968; 588346; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 30)
      Three letters to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Barbara Britton,., 1969; 588347; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence / Helen Gurley Brown,., 1976-1979; 588348 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Letters to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Laurie Philip Bruenn,., 1956-1962; 588349; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence / Judy Bublick,., 1955-1962; 588350; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence / Art Buchwald,., 1953-1977; 588351; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence / Ralph J. (Ralph Johnson) Bunche,., 1953-1961; 588352; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence / Edgar Rice Burroughs,., 1939; 588353; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 37)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows concerning the purchase of a Dachshund puppy.
    - General correspondence, "Ba",., 1948-1978; 588354; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence, "Be-Bi",., 1950-1978; 588355; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence, "Bl-Bo",., 1950-1977; 588356; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence, "Br",., 1948-1981; 588357; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence, "Bu-By",., 1954-1980; 588358; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, both personal and professional, of Abe Burrows. Includes miscellaneous Bs, not completely identified.
    - Correspondence / Herb Caen,., 1978-1979; 588359; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence / Sid Caesar, 588360; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 7)
      One holiday photograph card showing Sid Caesar with wife and child.
    - Correspondence / Godfrey Cambridge,., 1964; 588361; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence / Eddie Cantor,., 1946-1955; 588362 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence / Johnny Carson,., 1962-1964; 588363; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence / Jack Cassidy,., 1964 June 15; 588364; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Letter to Abe Burrows thanking him for an opening night telegram.
    - Correspondence / Henri Caubisens,., 1979-1980; 588365; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence / Bennett Cerf,., 1950 Nov 28; 588366; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 13)
      One letter to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Richard Chamberlain, 588367; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 14)
      One card to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Gower Champion,., 1955-1964; 588368; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Two letters to Abe Burrows from Marge and Gower Champion.
    - Correspondence / Carol Channing, 1967 and n.d; 588369; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence / Oona Chaplin,., 1977-1978; 588370; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 17)
      Correspondence [2 items] with Abe Burrows on the death of Charlie Chaplin.
    - Correspondence / Paddy Chayefsky, 1961 and n.d; 588371; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 18)
      Letters to Abe and Carin Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Maurice Chevalier,., 1955; 588372; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence / Edward Cheyfitz, 1955-1962 and n.d; 588373; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows, includes obituary and correspondence with Julia Cheyfitz after Edward Cheyfitz's death.
    - Correspondence / Harold Clurman,., 1959 Mar 26; 588374; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence / Alexander H. Cohen,., 1955-1969; 588375; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence / Noel Coward,., 1957-1964; 588376; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence / Fleur Cowles,., 1952-1963; 588377; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence / Alan MacGregor Cranston,., 1963-1965; 588378; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence / Cheryl Crawford,., 1955-1963; 588379; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence / Hume Cronyn,., 1952-1964; 588380; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence / Bing Crosby, 1961 and n.d; 588381; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 28)
      Letters, cards and photographs to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / John Crosby,., 1947-1961; 588382; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - General correspondence, "Ca-Ce",., 1953-1977; 588383; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - General correspondence, "Ch-Cl",., 1944-1978; 588384; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - General correspondence, "Co",., 1939-1978; 588385; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - General correspondence, "Cr-Cz",., 1951-1976; 588386; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence / Claude Dauphin,., 1960-1962; 588387; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence / Albert Dekker, 588388; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Poem with note [1 item] to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Olivia De Havilland,., 1962-1965; 588389; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 3)
      One letter and one postcard to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Agnes De Mille,., 1952; 588390; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Correspondence [2 items] with Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Armand Deutsch,., 1946-1966; 588391; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence / Martin Dibner,., 1953-1958; 588392; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence / Howard Dietz,., 1953-1963; 588393; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Correspondence between Howard and Lucinda Dietz and Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Phyllis Diller,., 1970; 588394; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence / Robert Emmett Dolan,., 1951-1966; 588395; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence / Fifi D'Orsay,., 1950 Aug 1; 588396; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence / Kirk Douglas,., 1975-1977; 588397; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence / Dramatists Guild,., 1949-1960; 588398; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows and other papers including contracts, legal briefs, memos and newsletters.
    - Correspondence / Dramatists Guild,., 1961-1971; 588399; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence / Jimmy Durante,., 1947 Aug 22; 588400; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 14)
      One telegram to Abe Burrows.
    - General correspondence, "Da",., 1949-1981; 588401; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - General correspondence, "De-Di",., 1948-1982; 588402; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - General correspondence, "Do",., 1949-1980; 588403; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - General correspondence, "Dr-Dv",., 1949-1971; 588404; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence / Faye Emerson,., 1951-1956; 588405; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence / Robert Emmett,., 1950-1951; 588406; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - General correspondence, "E",., 1955-1979; 588407; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence / Nanette Fabray,., 1965-1977; 588408; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence / Clifton Fadiman,., 1954; 588409; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence / Douglas Fairbanks,., 1959-1961; 588410; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence / Jose Ferrer,., 1963; 588411; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence / Cy Feuer,., 1951-1978; 588412; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence / Henry Fonda, 1962 and n.d; 588413; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Two thank you notes to Abe Burrows for opening night messages.
    - Correspondence / Lynn Fontanne,., 1954-1956; 588414; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Two thank you notes to Abe Burrows for opening night telegrams.
    - Correspondence / Allen Funt,., 1968; 588415; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence / James C. Freund,., 1976-1978; 588416; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows concerning his complaints about apartment noise.
    - General correspondence, "Fa-Fe",., 1955-1980; 588417; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - General correspondence, "Fi-Fo",., 1951-1979; 588418; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - General correspondence, "Fr-Fu",., 1949-1980; 588419; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence / Pierre Galante,., 1962-1981; 588420; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence / Johan Galtung,., 1959-1964; 588421; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence / Ed Gardner, 1940-1950 and n.d; 588422; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Also one letter, 1980, to Burrows about Gardner by his sister.
    - Correspondence / Harold Gary,., 1966-1977; 588423; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence / Sir John Gielgud,., 1959 Dec 3; 588424; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 17)
      Thank you card to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Benedict Gimbel,., 1951-1966; 588425; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence / Peter Glenville,., 1959-1962; 588426; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 19)
      Three letters to Abe Burrows thanking him for opening night telegrams.
    - Correspondence / Arthur Godfrey,., 1964; 588427; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 20)
      One letter and one telegram to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Augustus Goetz,., 1954 Feb 15; 588428; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 21)
      Letter to Abe Burrows.
      Goetz, Ruth
    - Correspondence / Samuel Goldwyn,., 1951-1954; 588429; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 22)
      One telegram and three notes to Abe and Carin Burrows from Frances and Samuel Goldwyn.
    - Correspondence / Mark Goodson,., 1951-1962; 588430; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 23)
      Correspondence between Mark Goodson, Bill Todman and Abe Burrows.
      Todman, William S., 1918-1979
    - Correspondence / Adolph Green, 1964-1980 and n.d; 588431; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 24)
      Three letters to or about Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Evelyn Greene,., 1950s; 588432; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 25)
      Notes and memos by Abe Burrows to his secretary, Evelyn Greene.
    - Correspondence / Tammy Grimes,., 1964 Apr 20; 588433; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 26)
      Thank you note to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Lee Guber,., 1960-1969; 588434; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence with miscellaneous guilds,., 1949-1980; 588435; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 28)
      Correspondence between Abe Burrows and various writer's and directors guilds. Also some printed material mainly on the Musicians' Mutual Protective Association.
      American Guild of Variety Artists; Directors Guild of America; Radio Writers Guild
    - Correspondence / Sir Tyrone Guthrie,., 1961 Nov 13; 588436; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 29)
      One thank you letter for opening night wire to Abe Burrows.
    - General correspondence, "Ga-Ge",., 1940-1976; 588437; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - General correspondence, "Gi-Gl",., 1947-1977; 588438; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - General correspondence, "Go",., 1948-1982; 588439; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - General correspondence, "Gr-Gu",., 1948-1970; 588440; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence / Richard Halliday, 1962 and n.d; 588441; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Five letters from Richard Halliday and his wife Mary Martin to Abe Burrows.
      Martin, Mary, 1913-
    - Correspondence / T. Edward Hambleton,., 1972; 588442; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows about the play Galileo by Bertolt Brecht..
      Brecht, Bertolt, 1898-1956; Galileo
    - Correspondence / Oscar Hammerstein,., 1952-1963; 588443; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Correspondence between Oscar and Dorothy Hammerstein and Abe Burrows.
      Hammerstein, Dorothy
    - Correspondence / Otto Harbach, 1953 and n.d; 588444; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence / George Harris,., 1961-1965; 588445; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence / Julie Harris,., 1970-1974; 588446; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence / Moss Hart,., 1952-1964; 588447; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Correspondence between Moss and Kitty Hart and Abe Burrows. Also a memorial tribute to Moss Hart.
      Carlisle, Kitty, 1915-
    - Correspondence / Leland Hayward,., 1951-1964; 588448; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence / Ben Hecht,., 1950-1959; 588449; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Correspondence between Ben and Rose Hecht and Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Hertz Corporation,., 1965-1973; 588450; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows reflects his various disagreements with the car rental agency he used.
    - Judy Holliday Memorial correspondence,., 1966; 588451; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Notes, program, clippings and correspondence with Abe Burrows.
      Holliday, Judy
    - Correspondence / John Cecil Holm,., 1969-1973; 588452; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Files / United States. Congress. House. Committee on Un-American Activities,., 1951 Mar 20; 588453; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 13)
      Testimony of Abe Burrows before the Committee.
    - Files / United States. Congress. House. Committee on Un-American Activities,., 1950-1954; 588454; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Statements of Abe Burrows.
    - Files / United States. Congress. House. Committee on Un-American Activities,., 1951-1954; 588455; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Correspondence of Abe Burrows' lawyer, Martin Gang of Gang, Koop & Tyre.
      Gang, Martin
    - Files / United States. Congress. House. Committee on Un-American Activities,., 1951-1955; 588456; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Correspondence of Abe Burrows with the general public concerning his testimony before the committee and his stand on communism.
    - Correspondence / Lester S. Hyman,., 1964-1980; 588457; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - General correspondence, "Ha",., 1947-1979; 588458; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - General correspondence, "He",., 1950-1979; 588459; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - General correspondence, "Hi-Hol",., 1949-1977; 588460; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - General correspondence, "Hom-Hy",., 1948-1977; 588461; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - General correspondence, "I",., 1958-1977; 588462; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence / Hubert Miles Gladwyn Jebb, Baron Gladwyn, 1953 and n.d; 588463; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 23)
      Letters and invitations to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Belinda Dobson Jelliffe,., 1948-1962; 588464; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence / Nunnally Johnson, 1954-1955 and n.d; 588465; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows much of it about turning his Can-Can into a movie.
    - Correspondence / Barney Josephson,., 1947-1948; 588466; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Three letters and one telegram to Abe Burrows about booking him at the Cafe Society in New York City.
    - Correspondence / Martin Jurow,., 1954-1957; 588467; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - General correspondence, "Ja-Je",., 1945-1979; 588468; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence, "Ji-Ju",., 1947-1981; 588469; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence / E. J. (Ely Jacques) Kahn,., 1947-1970; 588470; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence / Dick Kallman,., 1963-1964; 588471; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence / Garson Kanin,., 1949-1981; 588472; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence / Irwin Karp,., 1965; 588473; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Letters to Abe Burrows and Karp's statement, as counsel to the Author's League of America, to the House Judiciary Committee on copyright.